footlocker.eu 2014-03-26

# Customer-Service-Privacy-Policy

At Foot Locker we are committed to protecting your privacy. The Foot Locker website ("site") is a Netherlands based website and takes reasonable care to comply with the requirements of the Dutch Data Protection Legislation. Foot Locker is registered with the Dutch Data Protection authorities (Commissie Bescherming Persoonsgegevens) under the number M1028227. 

**Before creating an account on our website, you need to agree to the fact that we collect your data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions.**  
Prior to creating an account or placing your order, you agree to the fact that we may store, process and use data collected on our website. Please note that we may also share and disclose such data globally within the Foot Locker group of companies, including companies based in the US. Foot Locker, Inc. and its controlled US subsidiaries are participants in the Safe Harbor program developed by the US Department of Commerce. The Foot Locker legal entities have certified that they adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles agreed upon by the US and the EU. 

**What information do we collect? How do we use it?**  
The information we obtain from customers helps us to personalise and continually improve your shopping experience at Foot Locker. We use the information to handle orders, deliver products, process payments, communicate with you and prevent or detect fraud or abuses. Moreover, we will share some of the information with carefully selected third parties who will assist us for certain services such as technical, logistical support or other functions. Other services provided by third party companies may include processing of credit/debit card payments, deliveries, providing customer services and marketing assistance. 

By accepting our Privacy Policy and placing your online order, you agree that both your details and those of the delivery name and address may be checked by third parties such as credit agencies. 

We may also ask specific additional information e.g. when you enter a contest or other promotional initiative on our website. 

If you would like, you can also fill out a customer profile. While not required, information obtained from the customer profile helps us to learn more about our customers and is used to improve our customers' shopping experience with us. You can choose not to provide certain information but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features and benefits. In addition, if you choose to opt in, it will be used to send you e-mail updates about new product releases, Foot Locker newsletters, upcoming sales, contests, promotions, events and other Foot Locker initiatives. We may also send you personalised marketing materials and e-mail communications. If at any time you wish us to stop contacting you, then simply change your agreement preferences under the "My Profile" option. We may share personal information with our website hosting partners, and other parties who assist us in operating our website or conducting Foot Locker business, as long as those outside parties agree to keep the information safe and confidential. We may also release your personal information to comply with the law, to enforce our website policies, or to protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. We may use your information for statistical purposes. 

**Payment information**  
When you place an order, personal data provided by you can be transferred to a payment provider (e.g. ReD), acting as data processor for such data. Such data are only processed by the payment provider in order to process your payment instruction. Your personal data will not be provided to third parties other than the Financial Institutions for the chosen payment method. 

We will not sell information about you as an individual or your personal usage of the site. 

**How does Foot Locker protect customer information? Security of information PLSE**  
Foot Locker has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information you provide. We encrypt your personal information, including your credit card number, when transmitting over the internet, using SSL (Secure Socket Layer), Secure Server Certification Authority RSA Data Security Inc. US and a VeriSign SSL to safeguard your Internet transactions. VeriSign, Inc. is a leading provider of Public Key Infrastructure and digital certificate solutions used by enterprises, websites and consumers to conduct secure communications and transactions over the Internet and private networks. Browsers that allow for SSL Technology Ordering from our website require the use of an SSL-compliant browser, such as Netscape 4.0 or later; Microsoft Internet Explorer 5.0 or later; 5.0 AOL client for PCs; and the 5.0 AOL client for Macs. You will not be able to use [Secure Mode] if you have an older version of an Internet browser that does not support secure transactions, of if your computer is located on a local area network (LAN) that uses a firewall that prohibits secure transactions. If [Secure Mode] is not possible, please select one of our off-line options to place your order. 

**Cookies:**  
Cookies are small text files that are being sent from a web server to your browser, and which can be saved on the hard drive of your computer. A cookie contains specific information, e.g. a unique ID number which can capture which web pages you visited. With this unique ID, we can track your orders while you are shopping on our site. In addition, cookies recognize whether you are a registered user, which allows us to provide you with focused information each time you visit our website 

If you do not register on our site or your do not place an order, it is still possible that we capture information regarding your use of our site, in order to improve the site for you. The usage, such as number of visits and pages most viewed, do not contain any individualised information or shopping behaviour. Such information will only be used internally to optimise our online services. 

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to prevent cookies from being stored. However if you do turn cookies off this will limit the service that we are able to provide to you. 

**Your consent**  
We reserve the right to amend, modify or change at any time and for any reason, our privacy policy and this privacy notice. In any such event, we will post the revised Policy on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

**Children**  
Foot Locker is concerned about the safety of children when they use the internet. 

We do not specifically collect information about children. We believe that children should get their parent's consent before giving out personal information. If you have not yet reached the age of 16 years, your parents will have to consent to your registration on our site and/or your placing an order. If you are concerned about your child's use of Footlocker.eu, we encourage you to use web-filtering technology to supervise your child's access to the site. 

**Updating Information/Your Account**  
In order to change or modify information previously provided by you, please go to the Footlocker.eu site, log into your profile, and update your information using the options provided. 

If you use the website, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer to prevent unauthorised access to your account. You agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account or password. 

**Access Right**  
You have a right to access the personal information held about you. To obtain a copy of this, please contact Customer Service per the details below. We may charge a small fee towards the cost of administering any request you make. 

**Organizational, Management and Control Model Pursuant to Italian Legislative Decree N. 231 of 2001**  
On the 30th of March 2010 the Board of Managing Directors of Foot Locker Italy S.r.l. has approved the Organizational, Management and Control Model pursuant to Italian Legislative Decree n. 231 of 2001 (hereinafter referred to as "Model 231"), including the Principles of the Model 231. 

The Model 231 represents an unicum of principles, rules and statements aiming at:  
\- influencing the internal functioning of the Company and the principles and values to conduct its business relationships with the outside world;  
\- preventing the commission or attempts to commit crimes as provided by the d.lgs. 231/2001 by means of an efficient management and control system. 

The Model 231 is a statement of Foot Locker's commitment to conducting business according to the highest ethical and legal standards in Italy. The senior management of Foot Locker Italy S.r.l. takes the Model 231 - and the related compliance with it by the associates and third parties - very seriously. 

As a result, in each ITA and ENG page we should be able to download two docs 

**Customer Service Contact Details:**  
**_By Phone:_** contact our customer service helpdesk, by dialing one of the below numbers based on your country: 

Country: | Phone Number: | Opening Hours:  
---|---|---  
United Kingdom | 0800-3316062 | Monday to Friday from 8AM to 8PM   
Saturday and Sunday from 9AM to 5PM   
France | 08 05 54 07 86  | Monday to Friday from 9AM to 9PM   
Saturday and Sunday from 10AM to 6PM   
Germany | 0800-5888232 | Monday to Friday from 9AM to 9PM   
Saturday and Sunday from 10AM to 6PM   
Belgium | 0800-81177 | Monday to Friday from 9AM to 9PM  
Saturday and Sunday from 10AM to 6PM   
Luxemburg | 800-26555 | Monday to Friday from 9AM to 9PM  
Saturday and Sunday from 10AM to 6PM   
Netherlands | 0900 2255 877 | Monday to Friday from 9AM to 9PM  
Saturday and Sunday from 10AM to 6PM   
Italy | 800 986936 | Monday to Friday from 9AM to 9PM  
Saturday and Sunday from 10AM to 6PM   
Spain | 800 600931 | Monday to Friday from 9AM to 9PM  
Saturday and Sunday from 10AM to 6PM   
  
**_E-mail:_** If you have questions you can contact us by email based on your preferred language:  

Country: | E-Mail:  
---|---  
English | [questions_en@footlocker.eu](mailto:questions_en@footlocker.eu)  
German | [fragen@footlocker.eu](mailto:fragen@footlocker.eu)  
French | [questions_fr@footlocker.eu](mailto:questions_fr@footlocker.eu)  
Dutch | [vragen@footlocker.eu](mailto:vragen@footlocker.eu)  
Italy | [domande@footlocker.eu](mailto:domande@footlocker.eu)  
Spain | [preguntas@footlocker.eu](mailto:preguntas@footlocker.eu)  
|   
  
**Option to Opt-out**  
You can always opt out of our email service by clicking the "please notify us" link in any email we send you. 

**Tell us what you think**  
Foot Locker welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please contact us via e-mail at questions@footlocker.eu 

**External Links**  
We may provide links to other sites, which will not be governed by this Privacy Policy. These sites may have their own privacy policies, which you should review before visiting them. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites. The terms and conditions herein do not apply to any such linked websites. Foot Locker does not endorse any linked websites, or the information, materials, products or services that are contained in or accessible through such linked websites. Foot Locker disclaims all warranties, express or implied, with respect to the information, materials, products and services that are contained in or accessible through linked websites, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose or non-infringement. You acknowledge and agree that Foot Locker is not responsible for the content, accuracy, legality, decency, copyright compliance, privacy practices, security or any other aspects of any such linked websites, and that the access or use of any such linked websites is solely at your own risk, and you hereby waive any and all claims against Foot Locker with respect to such linked websites.
